# Gustavo Escher Pires Mendes

# Petroleum Engineering Intern

Graduating in Petroleum Exploration and Production Engineering at the Universidade Estadual do Norte Fluminense Darcy Ribeiro (UENF). Trained in English. Has experience in university tutoring. Has notions of administrative assistance, computation, programming, philosophy, ethics, publishing, earth sciences, biological sciences, etc. Seeks to enter the job market as an intern in the E&P industry.

#### **Work History**

# 2021-10 -

#### **Engineering Intern**

## Current

National Petroleum Agency (ANP), Rio de Janeiro, RJ Works as intern at the Coordination of Rigs and Wells for the Superintendence of Operational Safety and the Environment, assisting the agency's regulatory body

#### 2019-10 -

#### **Engineering Intern**

2020-07

Schlumberger, Macaé, RJ

Worked as an intern in the Sales & Product Delivery area, also focusing on QSMS audit and COVID compliance.

#### 2019-03 -2019-10

### Undergraduate Research Scholar

Petrobras, Macaé, RJ

Worked as a fellow in the project: State-of-the-art Study of Reservoir Physical Modeling, in the area of three-dimensional reservoir modeling, using 3D graphic modeling and 3D printing tools.

# 2018-01 -

#### **Administrative Assistant**

2019-03

UENF, Macaé, RJ

 Worked as a fellow at the postgraduate secretariat of the Petroleum Exploration and Production Engineering Laboratory.

#### 2016-01 -

#### Tutor

2017-12

UENF, Campos, RJ

Worked as a tutor for the Technical Drawing I discipline, at the Civil Engineering Laboratory.

#### Education

#### 2014-08 -Current

# **Bachelor of Science: Petroleum Engineering**

State University of Northern Rio De Janeiro - RJ, Brazil

#### 2006-01 -

#### 2013-07

Hope School of English - GO, Brazil

**English Education** 

#### Contact

#### **Address**

Macaé, 27930805 Brazil

#### Phone

(22) 99863-5565

#### E-mail

gustavo.escher58@gmaill.com

#### LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/gustavo-mendes58

#### **Technical Profile**

- C++
- VBA (beginner)
- Microsoft Office
- Linux
- MATLAB
- R
- Power BI
- Blender (beginner)
- Fusion 360

## **Competencies**

Regulatory Requirements

Researching knowledge

Safety processes and procedures